{
    "subject": "resource/RuPaul",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Electro_house",
    "human_readable": "RuPaul's genre is Electro house.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9545387625694275,
            "question": "Is RuPaul known for performing Electro house music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.749829113483429,
            "question": "What electronic music subgenre has RuPaul been associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7172463536262512,
            "question": "Which electronic dance music subgenre is associated with RuPaul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6475789546966553,
            "question": "What electronic dance music subgenre is RuPaul famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6296337842941284,
            "question": "What music genre is RuPaul known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4893941879272461,
            "question": "What genre of music defines RuPaul's musical style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.429788738489151,
            "question": "In what musical genre does RuPaul's music fall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41097813844680786,
            "question": "What kind of music does RuPaul primarily perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3808995187282562,
            "question": "Can you describe the type of music RuPaul creates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3668248653411865,
            "question": "What is the primary music style RuPaul is known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=RuPaul's genre is Electro house.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7651_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the type of music RuPaul creates?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7651_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music does RuPaul primarily perform?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7651_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what musical genre does RuPaul's music fall?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7651_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7651_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7651_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7651_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7651_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7651_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7651_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7651_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7651_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7651_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7651_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents mention RuPaul's work with EDM and  \"disco period, during which he melded the slick keyboards and ostinato strings popularized by artists like Sylvester and Gloria Gaynor into a campy take on the mechanical house music fashionable in the mid-\u201990s\", they don't explicitly state his genre is Electro House. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about RuPaul's career, including his work as a musician and the genres he has been associated with. While explicit mentions of \"electro house\" are not directly stated, the context discusses RuPaul's work in dance music and EDM (Electronic Dance Music), which includes elements that align with electro house. The documents describe his ability to blend different electronic music styles and produce \"sweet, inspirational dance music,\" supporting the inference that RuPaul's genre can be considered Electro house."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "While the provided text describes RuPaul's music as incorporating elements of EDM and house music, it also mentions his earlier disco period and highlights a blend of styles throughout his career. Labeling him solely as electro house oversimplifies his diverse musical journey.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}